[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Світлофор' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しん ごう"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Поверніть, будь ласка, на…' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "みぎ (へ|に), ひだり (へ|に)"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Водій' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うんてんしゅ"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Втомитися' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "つかれました"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Лікарня' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "びょういん"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Закривати, закрито' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Аптека' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "やっきょく"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Сказав “～”' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "といいました"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Прямо' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "まっすぐ"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Решта' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おつり"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Дуже' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とても"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Випадково' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぐうぜん"
    }
]
